{
    "subject": "resource/Integra_Live",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmingLanguage",
    "object": "resource/Apache_Flex",
    "human_readable": "Integra Live is written in Apache Flex.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.972431480884552,
            "question": "Can Integra Live be developed using Apache Flex?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9693938493728638,
            "question": "Is Apache Flex used to develop Integra Live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8762792348861694,
            "question": "Is Apache Flex a crucial component of Integra Live's development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6228165626525879,
            "question": "What programming language is Integra Live written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4255063831806183,
            "question": "What technology stack does Integra Live utilize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3947046101093292,
            "question": "What technology underpinns the functionality of Integra Live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3763943016529083,
            "question": "Which framework is employed for building Integra Live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3700290024280548,
            "question": "What platform or environment is Integra Live built upon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3193543553352356,
            "question": "What is the primary language used for creating Integra Live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29765835404396057,
            "question": "What is the programming environment used for developing Integra Live?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Integra Live is written in Apache Flex.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8297_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary language used for creating Integra Live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8297_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What platform or environment is Integra Live built upon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8297_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which framework is employed for building Integra Live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8297_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8297_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8297_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8297_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8297_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8297_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8297_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8297_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8297_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8297_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8297_37.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nReasoning:\n\n* The document mentions that \"The graphical front end is written using the open source Apache Flex framework.\" which directly supports the statement that Integra Live is written in Apache Flex."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information states, \"The graphical front end is written using the open source Apache Flex framework,\" which directly supports the claim that Integra Live's graphical front end is written in Apache Flex."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Integra Live is not written in Apache Flex, but rather the graphical front end of Integra Live is. The Integra Live application itself is built using open source software and open standards, as stated in the context information.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple passages state that the graphical front end of Integra Live is written using the open source Apache Flex framework.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The text explicitly states that the graphical front end is written using the open source Apache Flex framework, but this does not necessarily mean that Integra Live itself is written in Apache Flex. It only mentions that the graphical front end is, implying that other parts of the application might be written in different languages or frameworks.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that the graphical front end of Integra Live is written using the open source Apache Flex framework, not that Integra Live itself is written in it.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}